http://www.vitalenergi.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Energy Efficiency
Design, Build, Operate,
Trigeneration
(CCHP)
Privacy Policies
These are our privacy notices explaining how we collect and use your personal data. They describe the processing activities that are carried out by Vital Energi Ltd and the purposes for which these activities are performed.
We may update these privacy notices from time to time to ensure they are always up to date and accurate. Any changes we may make to our privacy notices will be posted on this page.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice explains what personal data Vital Energi collects from individuals who visit our website, contact us using our web forms, by email or through one of our social channels; or subscribe for our newsletter or other marketing communications. It also explains what information we collect automatically when you visit our website.
Download the full Policy here.
Privacy Policy for End Customers
This privacy notice explains what personal data Vital Energi collects from residents who we directly supply heating and hot water to.
Download the full Policy here
Download previous policies
Privacy Policy for Residents on the Leeds MSF Project
This privacy notice explains what personal data Vital Energi collects from residents on the Leeds MSF Project.
Download the full Policy here
Contact Us
If you'd like more information on our energy solutions and services then we'd be more than happy to help.
Our Technologies
As a mulit-technology provider we have the in-house expertise to provide the right solution for your project requirements.
Discover more
News Centre
Catch up on the latest Vital news and industry insights, all in one place.
Explore news
Case Studies
See how we’ve helped clients all over the UK solve their energy issues,
Read more
Careers
Vital Energi is a great place to work offering professional development and competitive salaries
